Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series II: Confessions I-N
  - Names: I
    - I Il, 7/1977 (Reel 43, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/8/1977
    - I Peng Seang, N/A (Reel 39, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 29/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 19/12/1976; 22/12/1976; 2 sections undated
    - I Poeurng Pounel, 25/11/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1978
    - I Soeurn, N/A (Reel 41, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1976; 9/8/1976; 16/8/1976; i section undated
    - Ieng Seitha, 16/12/1976 (Reel 40, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/5/1977; 3/1/1977(2); 16/2/1977(2)
    - Im Chhan, N/A (Reel 40, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/7/1977; 6/8/1977
    - Im Chhear, 26/9/1977 (Reel 40, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/10/1977
    - Im Choeurn, 8/9/1978 (Reel 41, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/6/1978
    - Im Chriv, 8/1977 (Reel 43, Frame 11)
    - Im Heng, 4/3/1978 (Reel 40, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/4/1978
    - Im Him, 3/2/1978 (Reel 39, Frame 22)
    - Im Khan, 30/11/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/12/1978
    - Im Kun, 21/3/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 14)
    - Im Ly, N/A (Reel 41, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/4/1978
    - Im Mann, 23/1/1977 (Reel 43, Frame 16)
    - Im Mom, 27/3/1978 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/5/1978; 26/5/1978
    - Im Mourn, N/A (Reel 40, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/2/1977; 16/2/1977(2); 17/2/1977
    - Im Nen, N/A (Reel 39, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/3/1978; 10/3/1978; 6/5/1978; 23/5/1978; 1 section undated
    - Im Oeur, 17/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1978; 1 section undated
    - Im Orn, 4/3/1977 (Reel 40, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/6/1977; 22/3/1977; 27/3/1977; 24/6/1977; 13/6/1977; 5/6/1977; 8/6/1977; 3/5/1977; 23/5/1977; 18/5/1977
      7/5/1977; 8/5/1977; 4 sections undated
    - Im Phal, 5/9/1975 (Reel 42, Frame 2)
    - Im Pronch, 27/9/1977 (Reel 41, Frame 3)
    - Im Sam Oeurn, 15/2/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 8/3/1977(3); 9/3/1977; 11/13/1977; 1/3/1977; 16/2/1977; 18/2/1977; 1 section undated
    - Im Sambath, 15/4/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 7)
    - Im Sambo, 30/7/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1978
    - Im San, 21/3/1978 (Reel 39, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/7/1978
    - Im Sokhun, 21/11/1975 (Reel 42, Frame 6)
    - Im Som Ol, 5/12/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/1/1979
    - Im Sot, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/11/1976(3)
    - Im Suy, 2/11/1977 (Reel 41, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/11/1977
    - Im Thy, N/A (Reel 40, Frame 11)
    - Im Voeurn, N/A (Reel 41, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/2/1977; 27/2/1977; 2/2/1977; 19/2/1977(2); 18/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 14/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 23/2/1977
      24/2/1977(2); 1 section undated
    - Im Yoeurn, 26/10/1977 (Reel 41, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1977; 1 section undated
    - Im Yoeurn, 10/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 13)
      Age: 78
      Dates of Confessions: 21/11/1978
    - Im Yoeurn, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 14)
    - Im Yueut, 28/8/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 10)
    - In An, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/3/1977
    - In Boeurn, 7/1/1976 (Reel 41, Frame 4)
    - In Chem, 27/1/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/3/1977; 8/3/1977(2); 9/3/1977
    - In Kim Ly, 22/11/1975 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - In Lay, N/A (Reel 41, Frame 14)
    - In Loch, 28/6/1975 (Reel 43, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/6/1975
    - In Muny, 13/6/1976 (Reel 41, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 18/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 29/7/1976(2); 8/8/1976; 6/8/1976(2); 11/8/1976; 17/8/1976
      13/8/1976 (2); 18/8/1976(2); 12/9/1976
    - In Mut, 2/2/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/2/1978; 4/2/1978
    - In Nat, 25/12/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/12/1978; 31/12/1978; 2 sections undated
    - In Neang, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 9)
    - In Phan, 7/7/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 4)
    - In Phon, 28/8/1977 (Reel 43, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1978
    - In Sa Ngot, 7/1/1976 (Reel 41, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/1976
    - In Sarun, 17/2/1978 (Reel 40, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1976; 30/3/1978; 7/4/1978
    - In Song, 7/6/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/6/1978
    - In Sophann, 2/8/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/2/1977
    - In Uth, 11/2/1977 (Reel 40, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1977
    - In Van, 1/3/1977 (Reel 39, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/4/1977
    - Ing Bun Hour, 12/3/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/3/1978; 4/4/1978; 4/1978; 1/4/1978; 4/1978; 5 sections undated
    - Ing Chheng Im, 12/12/1978 (Reel 42, Frame 21)
    - Ing Kheang, 20/10/1975 (Reel 43, Frame 2)
    - Ing Kim Song, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 6)
    - Ing Loeur, 14/6/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/6/1977
    - Ing Philo Sophary, N/A (Reel 42, Frame 8)
    - Ing Ro Situon, 15/9/1976 (Reel 39, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/10/1976; 2/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 21/10/1976
    - Ismael Asman, 2/1/1977 (Reel 39, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1977
    - It Bun Y, 17/2/1978 (Reel 40, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/3/1978 1 section undated
    - Ith L≥un, 6/8/1977 (Reel 41, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1977; 30/8/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Ith Man, 25/5/1976 (Reel 41, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/5/1978; 2/6/1978; 19/6/1978
    - Ith Phann, N/A (Reel 43, Frame 18)
    - Ith Sorn, 31/12/1976 (Reel 42, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/11/1976; 20/11/1976(2); 28/11/1976; 2/12/1976; 6/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 15/12/1976; 19/12/1976
      29/12/1976; 31/12/1976; 4/1/1976
    - Ith Yim, 9/7/1976 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/8/1976(2); 1/9/1976; 2/9/1976(2); 3/9/1976; 4/9/1976(3); 6/9/1976(2); 7/9/1976(2); 11/9/1976(6)
      8/9/1976; 12/9/1976; 13/10/1976; 14/10/1976; 6/11/1976; 8/9/1976(3)
    - Iv Eang, 12/7/1977 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/9/1977; 21/9/1977
    - Iv Hoeurn, 11/11/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 15)
    - Iv Phuon, 6/6/1978 (Reel 43, Frame 5)
    - Iv Senarak, 16/5/1977 (Reel 39, Frame 18)
    - Iv Touk, 3/1978 (Reel 40, Frame 8)
  - Names: J
    - James Willian Clark, 23/4/1978 (Reel 185, Frame 55)
      Nationality (if foreign): United States
    - John Dawson Demhirst, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 57)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1978; 13/10/1978
      Nationality (if foreign): CIA/British Intelligence
  - Names: K
    - Ka Bony, 1/12/1975 (Reel 57, Frame 2)
    - Ka Im, N/A (Reel 49, Frame 20)
    - Ka Loon, 5/5/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 30)
      Nationality (if foreign): Thailand / Thaas Island
    - Ka Thou, 27/3/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 4)
    - Kaing Choeun, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 15)
    - Kaing Hel, N/A (Reel 54, Frame 24)
    - Kaing Sopheap, N/A (Reel 58, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/8/1976
    - Kak, 8/3/1978 (Reel 76, Frame 11)
    - Kak Khim, N/A (Reel 48, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977
    - Kak Phat, N/A (Reel 59, Frame 2)
    - Kak Thek, 4/8/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1977; 15/8/1977
    - Kam Kaing Ly, N/A (Reel 54, Frame 25)
    - Kam Vun, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/5/1977
    - Kan Moun, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 5)
    - Kan Sim, N/A (Reel 50, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/10/1976; 17/10/1976(2); 20/10/1976(2); 21/10/1976(4); 23/10/1976(3); 24/10/1976; 26/10/1976
      29/10/1976; 30/10/1976; 1/11/1976; 1 section undated
    - Kang, N/A (Reel 51, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 18/10/1976(2); 1/10/1976; 2/10/1976; 3/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 10/10/1976
      12/10/1976; 11/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976(2); 24/10/1976; 13/10/1976
      16/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 21/10/1976(2); 23/10/1976
      27/10/1976; 1/11/1976; 4/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 6/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 14/11/1976
    - Kang Chak, 9/8/1977 (Reel 58, Frame 6)
    - Kang Chhan, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 8/11/1976(2); 9/11/1976; 17/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 30/11/1976; 1/12/1976
      5/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 12/12/1976; 13/12/1976
      15/12/1976; 20/12/1976
    - Kang Daung, N/A (Reel 57, Frame 1)
    - Kang GaΣk, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 14)
    - Kang Kan, 17/9/1977 (Reel 53, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/10/1977; 29/10/1977
    - Kang Lean, 11/8/1978 (Reel 47, Frame 14)
    - Kang Leap, 4/11/1976 (Reel 51, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/11/1976; 23/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 2/10/1976(2); 19/10/1976; 16/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 1/11/1976; 18/10/1976
      4/11/1976; 18/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 6/11/1976; 10/10/1976
    - Kang Lim Heang, N/A (Reel 53, Frame 12)
    - Kang Maut, 9/12/1978 (Reel 60, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1978; 14/12/1978
    - Kang Nhek, 10/1975 (Reel 50, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/10/1975
    - Kang Pat, 28/9/1976 (Reel 55, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 28/10/1976
    - Kang Phan, 29/1/1978 (Reel 46, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/3/1978 2 sections undated
    - Kang Savann, 31/1/1978 (Reel 49, Frame 12)
    - Kang Song, 2/2/1978 (Reel 60, Frame 12)
    - Kann Nan, N/A (Reel 45, Frame 14)
    - Kanτ Rin, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 18)
    - Kao, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 31)
      Nationality (if foreign): Palowai Island
    - Kao Manath, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 38)
    - Kao Men, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 16)
    - Kao Neal, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 13)
    - Kao Sam Aun, 4/9/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/9/1977; 20/10/1977
    - Kao Yi, 2/8/1976 (Reel 57, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/8/1976; 30/8/1976; 30/8/1976; 29/8/1976
    - Kar Lay, 8/1976 (Reel 46, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1976; 4/10/1976(2); 8/10/1976; 10/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976; 14/10/1976(2); 18/10/1976; 1 section undated
    - Kas, 16/9/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 16)
    - Kas, 23/7/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/12/1977; 15/12/1977
    - Kas Sou, N/A (Reel 57, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1977; 9/2/1977; 14/2/1977(2)
    - Ke Chheang, N/A (Reel 49, Frame 21)
    - Ke Chhun, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 22)
    - Ke Choeng Heng, 26/12/1977 (Reel 54, Frame 19)
    - Ke Keng Sy, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1977; 10/1/1977; 3/1/1977
    - Ke Kim Huoth, 21/2/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/6/1976; 22/1/1977; 16/7/1977; 22/7/1977; 30/3/1977; 13/1/1977; 9/11/1977; 9/11/1977; 29/11/1977; 2/12/1977; 29/4/1978
    - Ke Kun, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 6)
    - Ke Morn, 23/11/1977 (Reel 58, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1978; 8/2/1978
    - Ke Nan, N/A (Reel 51, Frame 11)
    - Ke Nhanh, 18/5/1978 (Reel 57, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/6/1978; 19/7/1978; 21/5/1978
    - Ke Not, 25/12/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 8)
    - Ke Sam, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 6)
      Age: 60
    - Ke San, 4/3/1978 (Reel 55, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/5/1978; 2/5/1978
    - Ke Seang, N/A (Reel 51, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/9/1978
    - Ke Sok, 8/1/1977 (Reel 59, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1977
    - Ke Thor, N/A (Reel 45, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1977; 1/1/1977; 27/1/1977; 8/1/1977; 29/12/1976; 16/12/1976; 19/1/1977; 1/2/1977; 10/2/1977; 19/1/1977; 18/3/1977; 16/3/1977; 13/1/1977
      5/1/1977; 4/1/1977; 5/1/1977; 9/1/1977; 11/1/1977; 13/1/1977; 14/1/1977
      16/1/1977; 17/1/1977; 19/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 23/1/1977; 24/1/1977; 26/1/1977
      27/1/1977; 30/1/1977
    - Ke Yen, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/3/1977
    - Ke Yoeurn, N/A (Reel 53, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/5/1977
    - Ke Yoeurn, 28/2/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 14/3/1977
    - Kea An, 13/4/1977 (Reel 48, Frame 6)
    - Kea Kan, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/8/1977; 1/10/1977; 11/8/1977; 2/scetions undated
    - Keang Soly, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 19)
    - Keang Vanny, N/A (Reel 59, Frame 11)
    - Keang Vong Doeurn, 4/5/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/8/1977; 12/9/1977; 19/9/1977
    - Kel Sophan, N/A (Reel 58, Frame 33)
    - Kem Koeun, 23/8/1977 (Reel 48, Frame 2)
    - Ken Chhaim, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 8)
    - Ken Socheat, 8/5/1977 (Reel 59, Frame 3)
    - Keng Chun, N/A (Reel 50, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 3/10/1976; 4/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 7/10/1976(2); 9/10/1976; 10/10/1976(2); 11/10/1976
    - Keng Ham, 28/3/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 26)
    - Keng Lun, 25/1/1978 (Reel 49, Frame 4)
    - Keo Bun, N/A (Reel 45, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/12/1977
    - Keo Chean, 26/2/1978 (Reel 61, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1978
    - Keo Chhan, 28/8/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 30)
    - Keo Chhem, N/A (Reel 57, Frame 39)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/3/1978; 26/3/1978; 27/3/1978; 28/3/1978
    - Keo Chheng, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 5)
    - Keo Ho, 26/2/1977 (Reel 44, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/3/1977; 16/3/1977; 20/3/1977
    - Keo Huan, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/8/1976; 19/8/1976; 20/8/1976; 22/8/1976; 21/8/1976(2); 23/8/1976; 26/8/1976; 11/9/1976(2); 13/9/1976; 14/9/1976(2); 3 sections undated
    - Keo Khan, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 108/1978
    - Keo Khon, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 17)
    - Keo Kong, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/10/1976; 29/10/1976(2); 30/10/1976; 21/10/1976(2); 26/10/1976(2); 22/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 25/10/1976(2); 27/10/1976(2); 28/10;/1976(2)
      24/10/1976; 31/10/1976; 29/10/1976; 29/10/1976; 30/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 1 section undated
    - Keo Kuon, 20/8/1977 (Reel 59, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/9/1977
    - Keo Ly Thong Huot, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1978
    - Keo Meas, 20/9/1976 (Reel 50, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1976; 24/9/1976(2); 25/9/1976(2); 26/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 8/10/1976
    - Keo Moeurn, 11/1975 (Reel 53, Frame 16)
    - Keo Muny, 15/10/1976 (Reel 49, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 24/11/1976; 28/11/1976; 10/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 1 section undated
    - Keo Nget, 11/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 17)
    - Keo Nhiv, 24/7/1977 (Reel 50, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/8/1977; 16/8/1977; 7/9/1977; 23/9/1977
    - Keo Oun, 25/2/1978 (Reel 57, Frame 4)
    - Keo Phat, 9/10/1978 (Reel 57, Frame 32)
    - Keo Phean, 20/10/1976 (Reel 46, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/7/1977; 3/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Keo Pich, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 26)
    - Keo Run, 24/1/1977 (Reel 44, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/2/1977; 10/2/1977(2); 11/2/1977
    - Keo Sam Ath Van, 12/2/1978 (Reel 60, Frame 11)
    - Keo San, 3/6/1978 (Reel 58, Frame 20)
    - Keo Sarin, N/A (Reel 58, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/4/1978
    - Keo Saroeurn, 4/1977 (Reel 55, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/6/1977; 1 section undated
    - Keo Sary, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 17/3/1977
    - Keo Sra'Rn, 4/1/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/1/1977; 29/1/1977
    - Keo Sucheat, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/5/1977; 14/1/1978; 26/2/1978
    - Keo Tai Seng, 4/1978 (Reel 58, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/5/1978; 9/5/1978; 1 section undated
    - Keo Thon, 18/1/1976 (Reel 54, Frame 23)
    - Keo Tonh, 19/1/1978 (Reel 57, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/1/1978
    - Keo Veng, 17/5/1977 (Reel 60, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/5/1977
    - Keo Yan, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/3/1977; 17/3/1977
    - Keo Yun, 12/9/1976 (Reel 50, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/1/1977; 3 sections undated
    - Kep Mol, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/10/1976
    - Kep Siyet, 19/6/1978 (Reel 56, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1978
    - Kep Sophon, 2/7/1977 (Reel 46, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/8/1977; 22/8/1977
    - Kerry George Hamill, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 58)
      Nationality (if foreign): CIA/New Zealand Int.
    - Ket Chakun, N/A (Reel 50, Frame 1)
    - Ket Pann, N/A (Reel 45, Frame 16)
    - Keth Chau, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/3/1977; 20/3/1977; 22/3/1977; 1/4/1977; 21/4/1977
    - Keut Khan, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 16)
    - Key Khem (Reel 53, Frame 20)
    - Khan Phirun, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 25)
    - Khanm Sirak Phann, 21/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 28)
    - Khann, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 7)
    - Khann, 23/11/1977 (Reel 46, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/11/1977
    - Khann Khom, 9/7/1978 (Reel 49, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/7/1978
    - Khann Nath, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 15)
    - Khann Tam, 30/11/1978 (Reel 60, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/12/1978
    - Khat Chhon, 18/8/1976 (Reel 47, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/1/1977; 27/12/1976; 24/12/1976
    - Khat Mao, 31/1/1978 (Reel 50, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/1978; 18/2/1978
    - Khay Heng, 25/2/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/6/1977
    - Khay Sal, 27/9/1978 (Reel 58, Frame 12)
    - Kheam Kruth, 17/3/1978 (Reel 46, Frame 22)
    - Kheang Buoy, 7/1976 (Reel 52, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1976; 8/8/1976(5); 6/8/1976; 8/9/1976(9); 13/9/1976(4); 12/9/1976; 14/9/1976(3); 15/9/1976; 1/9/1976; 17/9/1976
      18/9/1976(2); 21/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 24/7/1976; 28/8/1976; 2/10/1976
      9 sections undated
    - Kheang Heng, N/A (Reel 49, Frame 24)
    - Kheang Sim Horn, 24/10/1978 (Reel 53, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/10/1978; 3/11/1978; 18/12/1978
    - Kheav An, 16/3/1977 (Reel 55, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/8/1977; 25/9/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Kheav Chheang, N/A (Reel 48, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/8/1976; 11/8/1976(4); 13/8/1976(2); 28/8/1976; 29/8/1976; 30/8/1976(2); 1/9/1976; 17/11/1976; 41 sections undated
    - Kheav Chhoeurn, 12/10/1976 (Reel 57, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/10/1976; 12/10/1976(2)
    - Kheav Hok Sor, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 34)
    - Kheav Rum, N/A (Reel 58, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/9/1976; 3/9/1976;3/8/1976; 4/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 20/8/1976; 30/8/1976; 27/8/1976; 23/8/1976; 27/8/1976; 3/9/1976
    - Kheav Sarat, 22/8/1975 (Reel 59, Frame 6)
    - Kheav Socheata, 11/1/1976 (Reel 52, Frame 11)
    - Kheav Soeurn, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 22)
    - Kheav Sophang, N/A (Reel 52, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/12/1977; 11/12/1977
    - Kheav Tha, 29/7/1976 (Reel 55, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1976; 18/8/1976; 16/8/1976; 1 section undated
    - Kheav Thin, 18/2/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/3/1977; 21/3/1977; 1/9/1977
    - Kheav Tuow, 4/7/1978 (Reel 58, Frame 13)
    - Kheav Vong, 12/12/1977 (Reel 48, Frame 12)
    - Kheav Yos, 28/3/1977 (Reel 58, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/7/1977; 22/7/1977
    - Khek Pen, 21/6/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/7/1977; 21/8/1977; 10/9/1977; 8/9/1977; 21/9/1977; 13/9/1977; 5/9/1977; 7/9/1977; 19/9/1977; 4 sections undated
    - Khek Sun, 12/6/1978 (Reel 55, Frame 4)
    - Khem Huot, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 7)
    - Khem Pheap, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/8/1977; 1 section undated
    - Khem Pheap, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 8)
    - Khem Rin, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 19)
    - Khen Khorn, 1/1/1978 (Reel 56, Frame 36)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1978
    - Kheng Khan, N/A (Reel 51, Frame 12)
    - Kheng Kim Chhai, 8/1/1977 (Reel 59, Frame 9)
    - Kheng Ny, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 20)
    - Khenh Yim Suor, 5/9/1975 (Reel 54, Frame 13)
    - Khiev Em, N/A (Reel 53, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/1/1977
    - Khiev Ny, 12/9/1977 (Reel 45, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/12/1977
    - Khiev Sakour, 8/12/1976 (Reel 47, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/1/1977; 28/1/1977
    - Khiev Serei Vut, 8/3/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/3/1977; 25/3/1977; 29/3/1977(2); 26/8/1977
    - Khiev Sieng, 16/5/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 16)
    - Khiev Soth, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976; 22/9/1976; 23/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 24/9/1976(2); 29/9/1976; 5/10/1976; 6/10/1976; 11/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 14/10/1976
      16/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 19/10/1976(2); 1 section undated
    - Khiev Sun, 22/8/1975 (Reel 48, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/12/1975; 11/1/1976; 8/9/1975
    - Khim Baring, 8/1975 (Reel 49, Frame 27)
    - Khim Chea, 16/5/1977 (Reel 51, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/7/1977
    - Khim Chey, 3/1975 (Reel 48, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1975; 1 section undated
    - Khim Chey, 3/1975 (Reel 54, Frame 20)
    - Khim Chum, N/A (Reel 57, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/11/1978; 30/10/1978
    - Khim Chuon, N/A (Reel 54, Frame 5)
    - Khim En, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/6/1977; 26/6/1977
    - Khim Hea, 10/6/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 14)
    - Khim Huon, 17/5/1977 (Reel 59, Frame 5)
    - Khim Huoth, 17/7/1977 (Reel 48, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/9/1977; 14/9/1977; 23/7/1977
    - Khim Khann, 18/3/1977 (Reel 51, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1978; 27/4/1978
    - Khim Khann, 19/3/1978 (Reel 56, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/4/1978
    - Khim Khem, 19/3/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 12)
    - Khim Khim, N/A (Reel 53, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/6/1977
    - Khim Khon, 29/4/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 5)
    - Khim Kim San, 11/7/1977 (Reel 49, Frame 11)
    - Khim Muth, N/A (Reel 49, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/7/1978
    - Khim Orn, N/A (Reel 57, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/9/1976(4); 13/9/1976; 9/10/1976(2); 1 section undated
    - Khim Phuong, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 11)
    - Khim San, N/A (Reel 46, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/12/1976; 28/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 5/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 10/12/1976; 12/12/1976; 12/12/1976; 14/12/1976
      16/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 20/12/1976; 29/12/1976; 3/1/1977; 4/1/1977
    - Khim Sarun, 27/7/1976 (Reel 56, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1976(15); 20/8/1976(10); 21/8/1976; 6 pages undated
    - Khim Sea, 25/4/1977 (Reel 57, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/4/1978; 28/6/1978
    - Khim Song Ly, 17/7/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/8/1977; 10/8/1977
    - Khim Teng Long, 25/3/1977 (Reel 56, Frame 25)
    - Khim Yi, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1978; 18/2/1978
    - Khim You, N/A (Reel 56, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/7/1977
    - Khin Khim, N/A (Reel 49, Frame 23)
    - Khin Mom, N/A (Reel 55, Frame 24)
    - Khin Vannak, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 10)
    - Khlauk Chan, 9/1977 (Reel 52, Frame 23)
    - Khlauk Say, N/A (Reel 47, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 5/1/1977; 6/1/1977; 18/1/1977; 19/1/1977(2); 22/1/1977; 10/12/1976; 25/12/1976; 17 sections undated
    - Khlauk Srean, N/A (Reel 48, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/12/1975; 16/12/1975
    - Khlauk Y, 12/11/1977 (Reel 55, Frame 8)
    - Khlerng Ho, 14/6/1977 (Reel 46, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/8/1977; 1 section undated
    - Khloeng Chin, N/A (Reel 58, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/10/1976
    - Khoem Chhum, 13/8/1978 (Reel 54, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/9/1978
    - Khoem Kong, N/A (Reel 44, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/12/1977